<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Elation Music]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Elation Music]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-elation-music/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 02:29:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/the-elation-music/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time to Change!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Time to Change!</h1><p>We posted earlier this week a segment regarding the bands past and more importantly our future plans. We have been blown away by the reaction we got from everybody and we want to thank those who showed us support. Whilst riding this wave, Yesterday we hit our biggest milestone to date as we opened up the beer hall stage for this years INDIEPENDENCE Music & Arts Festival. Not only was this the first time we played the festival but we also took the opportunity to launch our brand new original band 'THE ELATION'. We played a host of new music and we loved every minute of it. We have so much news to share with you over the next couple of weeks and we promise to keep you all posted on our exciting new journey. Until then here's one of our favourite shots from indie16 of our fans at the first ever 'The Elation' show.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5e7cc8cd-bb0e-4053-babb-70810cda56a5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5e7cc8cd-bb0e-4053-babb-70810cda56a5.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">43a88879-2214-4e5e-a5da-d6de9736b1b6</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 02:29:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The Elation are an original music act hailing from Cork, Ireland.Radio friendly floor fillers and high energy live shows are pushing UV5 forward to becoming the most exciting act in Ireland, the UK, and Europe.Infectious pop/funk and dance tracks, written and performed by the band, are making UV5 a red-hot prospect for major festivals, venues and even more sell out shows.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/the-elation-music/the-elation-are-an-original-music-act-hailing-from-cork-ire/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">38afab09-6000-417b-9df2-ec36fd318092</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 23:55:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>